https://www.tctimes.com/site/privacy.html

Fenton, MI
(48430)
Today
Mostly cloudy skies. High 47F. Winds N at 5 to 10 mph..
Tonight
Periods of rain. Low 38F. Winds ENE at 5 to 10 mph. Chance of rain 100%. Rainfall around a quarter of an inch.
OBITUARIES
PRIVACY POLICYThank you for visiting the web sites of the Tri-County Times and its parent company, Rockman Communications. We encourage you to read the following information to learn what information is retained when you visit our sites and how that information is safeguarded and utilized.Information Automatically Gathered About All Visitors:Like nearly every medium, we collect user-specific information on which pages consumers access or visit. This information is used to generate aggregate reports that help determine the value of and interest in the various web sites we provide. We use the information we collect to continuously improve the content and design of our web pages. We can build a better site if we know which pages our users are visiting, how often they visit and how long they stay on a page. Our web servers automatically collect limited information about your computer’s connection to the Internet, including your IP address when you visit our sites. Your IP address does not contain personally identifiable information, nor does it identify you personally. We use this information to deliver our web pages to you upon request, to tailor our sites to the interests of individual users, and to measure traffic volume within our sites. To help make our sites more responsive to the needs of visitors, we may utilize a standard feature of browser software called a “cookie,” a small piece of computer code that is left on your hard drive when you visit our site. Browsers generally recognize when a cookie has been sent to your computer and give you the option to refuse or allow it. A cookie does not actually identify you, just the computer that you are using to access our site. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive. We use cookies to help us tailor our site to your needs so we can deliver a better and more personalized service. It is a cookie, for example, that allows us to deliver to you any requested information each time you visit a site. In addition, we can access cookies later in your current session or in a later session on our site in order to improve your visitor experience to our web site, as in the following examples:Account RegistrationIf your use of a component of the site requires you to register, a cookie will be used to automatically identify you as a registered user when you are visiting our site. These cookies are known as persistent cookies and continue on your computer after the initial session in which they are created. This cookie allows us to maintain information containing the products (like photo reprints) or services (such as placing a classified advertisement or signing up for home delivery) you are purchasing while you are online. To limit unauthorized access, this cookie, also called a session cookie, expires whenever you exit a browser session. Like many other commercial sites, our sites may utilize an electronic file called a web beacon to count users who have visited a page or to recognize users by accessing certain cookies. Our site and/or our partner web sites use web beacons for auditing purposes and to collect information from the websites of certain partners. Information recorded through these web beacons is used to report anonymous individual and/or aggregate information about our users from our partners. Aggregate information may include demographic and usage information.About Third Party AdvertisingWe may use third-party advertising companies to present ads when you visit our Web Site. These companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this Web Site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses’ privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information.Information Gathered by Voluntary SubmissionTo make use of certain features on our web sites (such as contests, story comments, letters to the editor, personalized web pages, daily deals and other interactive forums and blogs) visitors need to register and to provide certain information as part of the registration or participation process. We may ask, for example, for your name, e-mail address, gender, age, and zip code, and we might request information on your interest in sports, personal finance, the performing arts, and the like. The information you supply will help us offer you more personalized features, to tailor our sites to your interests and make them more useful to you. The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. But if you do not supply the information we need, we may be unable to provide you with services and content we make available to other visitors to our sites.E-mails from UsUpon registering with our website, you may begin receiving communications from us. In addition, if you have signed up for any of our automated account services, such as daily deals and others, we will send you transactional e-mails regarding the status of your account, including confirmations, notices of expiration and renewal and other related electronic correspondence. If you have signed up for any of our e-mail newsletters, you may stop receiving them if you follow the “unsubscribe” instructions. We may send you an e-mail inviting you to participate in subscriber or website user surveys. Such surveys greatly help us improve our services and the value of our web sites. Any information you give us in those surveys will not be shared with any third parties except in aggregate form.What We Do With the Information We Gather About YouWe or one of our affiliated companies may perform statistical, marketing and demographic analyses of our delivery subscribers and their subscription patterns. In addition, we may generally inform our advertisers about our subscriber base. When we present information to our advertisers -- to help them understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our websites -- it is generally in the form of aggregated statistics on traffic to various pages within our sites. We will not share individual user information with third parties unless the user has specifically approved the release of that information. In some cases, we contract with third parties to provide services on our behalf, including credit-card and bill processing, shipping, e-mail distribution, list processing and analytics or promotions management. We provide these third parties only with the information necessary for them to perform their specific services. These service providers are restricted from using this information in any way other than to provide services to us, and they may not share this information with any one else nor may they resell this data.Compliance with Legal ProcessWe may disclose personal information if we or one of our affiliated companies is required by law to disclose personal information, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to comply with a law or some legal process, to protect or defend our rights and property, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our web sites or to protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.AffiliationsWe are affiliated with other online companies, some of which feature our branding; in addition there are numerous links to third parties contained on our site. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to those companies.Due to the continually evolving nature of the internet, policies, processes and procedures evolve also. If we deem it necessary to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the changes before they take effect if we believe that the change in the way we use your personal information is significant in nature.EEAThis Site is not intended for use by persons located within the European Economic Area (EEA). We do not request or accept personal information concerning or supplied by persons who are located within the EEA at the time they access this Site. If you have accessed this Site from within the EEA, you should immediately discontinue your use. If you have supplied personal information to us in violation of this provision, whether through the registration of new user accounts or otherwise, please contact us at gdpr@tctimes.com.Last updated on 6/5/18Rockman Communicationsdba Tri-County Times
